astrologyanswers.com 2015-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Astrology Answers Astrological Horoscope Readings

**AstrologyAnswers.com Privacy Policy**   
Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information

**Last Updated July 10, 2013.**

Thank you for visiting AstrologyAnswers.com (the “Website”). This notice explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. Your use of the Website constitutes your acceptance to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

**FOR ENTERTAINMENT ONLY**

**REMEMBER THAT ASTROLOGYANSWERS.COM IS FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY. YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER TO USE THIS SERVICE. ALL CREDIT CARD PURCHASES MUST BE MADE BY THE CARD HOLDER. AT ASTROLOGY ANSWERS WE WANT YOU TO ENJOY AND BENEFIT FROM YOUR REPORT. WE MAKE EVERY EFFORT TO PROVIDE YOU WITH HELPFUL ADVICE. HOWEVER, THIS INFORMATION SHOULD NOT BE USED IN PLACE OF ANY RECOMMENDATIONS BY MEDICAL, LEGAL, OR FINANCIAL PROFESSIONALS OR OTHER PROFESSIONAL COUNSELORS. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO EVALUATE ANY INFORMATION, OPINION, ADVICE OR OTHER CONTENT AVAILABLE ON ASTROLOGY ANSWERS.**

**Personal Data: Astrologyanswers.com collects personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) in two categories:**

AstrologyAnswers.com collects information in two categories:

  * Your First Name, E-mail Address, Star Sign, Wish, Birthdate, Gender, Marital Status, and Work Status which may be used to personalize communication with you.

  * Name, Postal Address, Phone and Credit Card Information - provided by you when purchasing our Full Report. There is no obligation to provide this information or to purchase a Full Report.

Aggregate and Anonymous Data: We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e. generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac) and the domain name of your Internet service provider. Aggregate and Anonymous Data we may collect includes, but is not limited to, the total number of visitors to the Website, the number of visitors to each page of the Website, device identifier and hardware information, IP address, browser type and language, cookie information, system type, whether or not you have enabling software to access certain features, access times, referring website URLs and other information about your interaction with us. Astrologyanswers.com may analyze this data for trends and statistics, but such information will be maintained, used in aggregate form only and it will not contain Personal Data other than an IP address. We may use such Aggregate and Anonymous Data to analyze trends to better administer the Website. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.

**How We Use and Disclose the Information.**

We will use the Personal Data you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Your First Name, E-mail Address, Star Sign, Wish, Birthdate, Gender, Marital Status, and Work Status may be used to personalize communication with you. In addition, we may send to you e-mails offering products or services which we think you may be interested in or to send you information related to your report or star sign. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please contact us at [support@astrologyanswers.com](mailto:support@astrologyanswers.com) or click the unsubscribe link on the top of any communication from Astrologyanswers.com.

We may disclose your Personal Data in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims. We may also disclose your Personal Data when we believe it is necessary or desirable in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, and/or to protect our rights and property.

You have the option to purchase an in-depth Astrological Report from ASTROLOGY ANSWERS. There are a number of products and services that are sold here at ASTROLOGY ANSWERS, but there is no obligation to purchase any.

**How We Share Your Personal Data.**

We will not share the personal information you provide except as comports with this Privacy Policy. As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). At times, we may also share your Personal Data with third parties so that they may notify you of special offers, products and services that may be of interest to you. It is possible that we may rent, sell or otherwise transfer your Personal Data to such third parties. At any time, you can contact the Editor by e-mail to [support@astrologyanswers.com](mailto:support@astrologyanswers.com) to request that we not share your Personal Data with third parties.

Our business needs may change from time to time and we reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

Our operations and maintenance contractors sometimes have limited access to your Personal Data in the course of providing products or services to Astrologyanswers.com. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us with credit card processing, e-mail distribution technology, services, and/or content for the operation and maintenance of our Web site. Access to your Personal Data by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary for the contractor to perform its limited function for Astrologyanswers.com. We also contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors 1) protect the privacy of your Personal Data consistent with this Privacy Policy, and 2) not use or disclose your Personal Data for any purpose other than providing us with products and services as required by law. Astrologyanswers.com is committed to handling your customer information with high standards of information security. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

**Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information.**

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. We may also share aggregate information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies.

**Collection of Information by Others.**

Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should check the other sites' privacy notices since we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by them.

**Cookies.**

To enhance your online experience with us, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files placed on your hard disk by our web server to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other Personal Data unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to provide the Personal Data, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies as a conv enience feature to save you time, to understand how our site is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). You can opt to have your browser reject cookies without any effect on your use of our site. If you do that, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our site in order to participate in certain promotions. You should also know that companies that advertise on our web site (and their agents) might use their own cookies. This policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies.

**Web Beacons.**

Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons, which are also called single-pixel gifs. These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your Personal Data but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our website usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. Some of our Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.

**Discussions and Community Tools; Testimonials.**

You agree that any information you submit to us through AstrologyAnswers.com may be used for promotional purposes. Because of the public nature of some of our services, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. We may also use a limited amount of information, such as first name, last initial and your town and state in marketing materials on the website. Your registration constitutes consent to this use.

**International Users.**

If you are visiting AstrologyAnswers.com from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using AstrologyAnswers.com you authorize and specifically consent to the transfer of your personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. 

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Data.**

For instructions on how you can access the Personal Data that we have collected about you online, or how to correct any errors in such information, please send an e-mail to [support@astrologyanswers.com](mailto:support@astrologyanswers.com)

To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Special Note for Parents.**

AstrologyAnswers.com services may not be used by anyone under the age of 18. If you have concerns about this site or its services, wish to find out if your child is a member or has registered for one our services, please contact us at [support@astrologyanswers.com](mailto:support@astrologyanswers.com). If you believe that your child under 18 has gained access to our site without your permission, you may contact us [support@astrologyanswers.com](mailto:support@astrologyanswers.com).

**California Privacy Rights.**

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide Personal Data to the Website may request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at [support@astrologyanswers.com](mailto:support@astrologyanswers.com).

**How to Contact Us.**

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may e-mail [privacy@astrologyanswers.com ](mailto:privacy@astrologyanswers.com) or write to the following address:

10040 West Cheyenne Ave   
170-129 Las Vegas,  
NV 89129

All customer service related issues should be sent to [support@astrologyanswers.com](mailto:support@astrologyanswers.com) or you may write to us at:

10040 West Cheyenne Ave  
170-129 Las Vegas,  
NV 89129
